Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[Exhales]
OK. OK.
Oh. Whoa. whoa.
Hey. We need to talk.
I'm sorry. I can't.
KJ.
Seriously?
For days. I've been trying
to get you to talk to me.
and you choose now.
the day of the showcase?
OK. My timing
isn't the best.
Look. I get it.
OK. I screwed up.
and... and I'm the bad guy.
but I can't.
I cannot do this right now.
Tori: That's not what I was...
KJ: I gotta go.
Has Khalil signed in yet?
Hasn't the showcase
already started?
What you mean.
my son isn't here yet?
[Sound of audio track rewinding]
Hey. look. K.. I know this
ain't what you wanted to do.
but this gonna be good for you.
I thought we was done
lying to each other.
It was the only way I could
get you to talk to her.
I ain't got nothing to say.
Well. maybe she got
something to say to you.
It wasn't that long ago
where I was in
that same exact place.
Now look. We good!
We working on it.
I am just saying.
you gave me a chance.
Give her one.
Why are you so willing
to give her another one?
She walked out on both of us.
I'm not thinking about
me right now.
This is about you.
[Taps table]
I wasn't sure you'd come.
I keep my promises.
OK! All right.
Marqui: I'm so happy
that we are here.
Can you believe our boy
got me liking
this bougie-ass food
they got here?
That's crazy.
All type of smoothies.
I can't wait to taste it.
I only got time for a drink.
I'm hearing great things
about your showcase
this weekend.
You must be excited.
There it is.
The reason you're back.
The only reason I'm here is
because I want to tell you
that I'm sorry.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
What are you sorry for?
You sorry for having me?
You sorry for walking out
on me and Pop?
Yo. K.. come on. man.
Ah. Maybe you sorry
for all the nights
I spent wondering if I did
something to make you leave.
Ohh. I forgot.
You're probably sorry for
standing me up the last time
I tried to come see you.
Gotta go.
Yo. K.
No. Let him... let him go.
[Humming]
[Scoffs]
Are these really
the nicest dishes you own?
You sound like Jordan.
We're having
a dinner party tonight.
and I invited Preach and Amina.
But don't you worry.
Breonna and I are gonna
take care of everything.
Not worried. just confused.
Well. with you about
to leave for tour
and me about to be really
busy with my internship.
I just thought it'd be dope
if we all got together tonight
to have dinner here at
the Baker house. of course.
Does this have anything to do
with our conversation
earlier today?
[Scoffs]
You mean the one
where a certain friend of
mine questioned my happiness?
I think she was
just looking out for you.
You know. she sounds like
a really good friend.
Sometimes. But...
[Chuckles]
it's not... it's not
just about that.
Amina seems to think that
I went all corporate
and somehow lost myself
or lost my way.
but I just think that
people don't understand
what I got going with Breonna
or what I'm trying
to build with her.
so I was hoping by all
of us hanging out tonight
that they would.
Got it.
Almost like a power couple
coming-out party.
Almost.
What do you say?
I say it is time we show Breonna
we can have just as classy
a time as her Ojai friends.
Let's go.
You want to invite anyone else?
Uh. no. I say keep it small.
Less people. less drama.
Ooh. these are nice.
Yeah.
Hey. Got a minute?
You here to check out
your new office?
You know. I was actually hoping
for one with a window.
But. uh. I was hoping
we could talk.
You make a decision
about the job?
Not yet.
Then we got nothing
to talk about.
Our showcase is in 3 days.
OK. Cassius. I didn't
ask for your job.
And as soon as I got the offer.
I came and told you about it.
I know. But that doesn't
mean I'm not allowed
to feel some type of way
about all this.
That's fair. OK.
[Exhales]
But our kids. they
really need this showcase
to go well.
OK? They shouldn't suffer
because of us.
No. no. They shouldn't.
Well. look.
now isn't a good time.
I got a meeting soon. so...
OK. Um. what if you
came over tonight?
You could bring KJ.
We could have a drink.
get some work done.
or you could just
yell at me some more.
[Chuckles]
Tempting offer.
I will try to stop by if I can.
All right.
Ah. ha.
Nice. Where you off to?
I think you mean
where we're off to.
I'm not sure I meant that.
Coop invited us over
to the Bakers for dinner.
She wants us to get to know
Breonna or something.
I already know Breonna kind of.
And I really need
to study. so. yeah.
Well. time for a study break.
I barely seen you
since you been back.
Besides. Khalil will be there.
And I know everyone
wants to hear
everything about Dinsberg.
Definitely want to
do all of that.
but like I said.
finals are soon. and I...
And like I said.
Auntie Coop wants us there.
so we're going.
Now. go get changed.
Reliving the old
glory days. huh. Baker?
[Chuckles]
[No audio]
Cassius: So where do
I stand. Mr. Mosely?
London didn't think the Eagles
would win a single game.
much less make the playoffs.
Everyone had written them off.
Not everyone.
No. not everyone.
And. you know. thanks to you.
Beverly has
a winning team again.
And how does London
thank you. huh?
By offering your job to
some unqualified rich kid.
[Chuckles softly]
We'll just see about that.
Well. London seems pretty
set in his decision.
London still has boosters
to answer to.
And lucky for you. I'm finally
one of those boosters again.
I'd argue
the most important one.
Well. I haven't felt
too lucky lately.
so I will take
all the help I can get.
Just leave everything to me.
I've been waiting
for this for a long time.
Amina: We haven't talked
about what happened
at Dinsberg.
Everything OK?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
I just talked to my mom
earlier. but...
ain't nothing for you
to worry about.
What if I want to anyway?
I appreciate it.
but it's nothing.
Just more of the same.
What you need to talk about?
Something's for sure
going on with KJ and Amina.
I have proof.
What kind of proof?
I saw them in
the Beverly hallway.
and they were...
Hooking up?
Talking.
That's not exactly proof. Tori.
No. It's the way
they were talking.
They were very close.
How close?
That don't mean nothing.
You know KJ's kind of
a close talker.
It wasn't just that.
I caught him repeating
this Latin phrase
that's real specific
to Dinsberg.
And he's kind of a nerd. too.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Just this morning.
you were the one
who ratted out KJ and Amina
for keeping secrets.
And now you're all
"Don't worry about it"?
Keeping secrets. yeah.
but I didn't say
nothing about cheating.
Look. Amina and I ain't
really been great lately.
but she's not that
type of girl. Trust.
Jordan: Principal London.
come on.
Jordan. Cliff Mosely is
an important member of
the Beverly High community.
The board wants to hear him out.
Look. Principal London.
don't let this happen.
OK. not when my dad
hasn't left the hospital
since last night.
You can't expect him to be here
with everything going on.
That's exactly the point.
Jordan.
Your father's right.
With all that your family's
going through. it's best
that he and you.
for that matter.
put your energy
where it's most needed.
That's at the hospital
and at home.
This is ridiculous. Don't tell
me you're buying this bull crap.
Cliff:
The Beverly Eagles need
a coach able to focus
on the field.
Right now your father
just isn't that man.
Principal London.
Coop: Jordan?
Yo. come on.
[Slaps counter. claps]
Can we pick up the pace
a little bit?
Breonna's gonna be here
any minute with the food.
Yes. Uh. are you sure
you just
don't want me to whip out
the Blacktop
and grill up some smashers?
Layla: Jordan.
this isn't burger night. OK?
I told you this is
an elegant affair.
Right you were. my
dear. Right you were.
Coop. please forgive
my rudeness.
Coop: [Mock laughs]
All right.
You might move a little
faster if you don't talk.
Want to give that a try?
Listen. why are you so nervous?
It's just dinner.
I'm not nervous.
I just want tonight to go well.
Are these spots? What?
Why am I seeing spots?
OK. here's a trick.
Pour some wine in the glass.
you won't see the spots. OK?
And maybe have some
and relax. OK?
Tonight's gonna be great.
Everybody likes Breonna.
Mm-hmm. even though
she doesn't laugh
at any of my jokes.
I mean. everybody loves Breonna.
I'm not worried about that.
Wait. Does Breonna
not like us?
Are we not mature enough
for her?
Jordan: So that's why she
doesn't think I'm funny.
You know. those
elite types. they just...
they never get
my simple folk humour.
You know what. I don't like
either one of you right now.
And for the record.
Breonna didn't grow up
swimming in some pool
in Beverly Hills
like some "simple folk" I know.
She's not too different
from me. all right.
so y'all can kill
all the fancy talk.
[Doorbell rings]
And now she's here.
OK. OK. And what is this?
A little smoked duck
with some cherry glaze.
Sorry. girl.
The only thing Coop told me
about this dinner
was that it was tonight
and that we had to hurry up.
So I hope this will do.
I mean. Charcoal
& Ash? Nice!
I did not know that
they did takeout.
Breonna: You know. they do
when your firm handled
their payroll case.
Coop: All right. chill.
You acting like you
never seen food before.
Jordan: Hold on. now.
The boxes have vents.
That is a clutch move.
Keeps the potatoes crispy.
Ha!
Very fancy.
What's going on?
Coop and Breonna are
treating us to dinner.
Yeah. Preach and Amina
are on their way.
Uh. you cool if I skip?
I'm not too hungry.
I'm sorry. Do you smell
the truffle barbecue rub
on those wings?
Is everything OK?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Uh. just a rough day.
Ah. Well. you're about
to have a great weekend.
I just got word that
the assistant coach at Stanford
will be at the showcase.
-For real?
-Mm-hmm.
That's great. but. Coach.
you know my test scores...
I know. I know.
And I can't promise
you anything.
But when you impress
the hell out of him.
like I know you will.
maybe he'll tell the coach
you're someone
worth reevaluating with
the admissions office.
Thanks. Coach.
I needed some good news today.
[Sniffs]
Just keep up the good work
and there'll be more
to come. all right?
Just like these wings.
Check that out.
Bet you're hungry now.
We got wings!
Coming in hot.
Coop: Oh. wow.
Layla: Oh. great.
[Indistinct chatter]
KJ: Careful Jordan doesn't
try to steal those. too.
We've been over this.
Jordan did not steal my job.
It was offered to him.
Well. he could've said no.
Anyway. how'd the meeting
go with that booster?
[Chuckles softly]
I think the only person
that hates the Bakers
more than Cliff Mosely
is my dad.
Why? What did he say?
It was more of a gut feeling.
Well. well. did he say
he could help out?
[Sighs]
I mean. he did.
but I don't think Cliff's
the type of person
we want helping us.
Besides. Jordan
hasn't made a decision.
We don't even know
which way he's leaning.
Is there any way that
we can find out?
[Doorbell rings]
Amina. hi!
Coop: Hey. champ.
Preach: Hey.
Layla: Wow. Amina.
I haven't seen you
since your first day back.
Well. here I am.
[Music playing]
OK. Um. how...
or how is it? Are you...
are you loving it out there?
I mean. there's not
a lot to tell. So...
Coop: Uh. what ever happened
to the paper you was writing?
Well. some idiots at
the school paper
don't know what good writing is.
I doubt they even read it.
They definitely
read it. all right.
[Both chuckle]
Breonna: Has Coop told you
that I'm a Boardley Bear?
Boardley's their rival.
by the way.
I had the best time at school.
I bet you can't wait
to get back.
[Chuckles]
I'd leave right now if I could.
[Chuckles softly]
Um. are... are you in town
for long or...?
Just a few more days.
I still have that dead week
to study before finals.
Really? Wow! A dead week.
I had friends at Dinsberg.
It was intense.
They never had a dead week.
Amina: Friends? I thought
you said you were rivals.
Breonna: In sports. yeah.
but not in real life.
They were lucky if they
had two days to study.
Guess it's a new thing.
[Chuckles]
You know how progressive
Dinsberg says they are.
Right.
Amina: If you will excuse me.
Preach: Mm-hmm.
Sorry.
Dog. you notice
anything off about Amina
since she been back?
I've barely seen her all week.
That's the point.
I mean. don't it seem like
she been trying to avoid us?
Nah. she just busy. Nothing
wrong with working hard.
I like to think she
learned that from me.
Preach. she was so excited
about Dinsberg.
and now every time we
bring it up.
she get upset.
Red flag?
Maybe something
happened at school?
Coop: Whatever it is.
I think it's
something she ain't telling us.
Amina: OK.
What kind of food is this?
Uh. barbecue fusion.
Khalil: What's that?
Amina: Rich people food.
Coop: Excuse me?
Layla: Well. it looks amazing.
I can't wait.
Jordan: Yes.
Coop: Ooh.
Where are we supposed to sit?
Oh. we figured it'd get
a little crowded.
so we set up on the side
patio for you and Khalil.
Yeah. I... I think we've
outgrown the kids' table.
We'll sit here.
[Indistinct chatter]
Amina: See? Plenty of room.
Khalil: Mm. So cozy.
Well. I would like to make
a little toast to Coop.
I hope you guys are just
as proud of her as I am.
Jordan: Taught her
everything she knows.
[Laughter]
Preach: Well. as long as
we're talking about proud...
Dad. don't.
You better get used to me
being proud of you.
You're gonna do
some great things.
And Dinsberg is just the start.
Cheers.
You know. your school has
a really good pre-law club.
if you ever wanted to follow
in Coop's footsteps.
Yeah. No offence. but
I want to help our people.
not corporations.
Coop: Amina. if you want
to sit with the adults.
you need to act like one.
No. babe. that's fair.
Representing corporations is
a big part of what my firm does.
Same goes for the firm
Coop's interning with.
That's true.
But once she graduates
and we're able to open
our own firm.
eventually we will
be able to focus
on giving back
to the community more.
Eventually. Right.
My bad.
I just assumed people stayed
in their high-paying
jobs until they were
rich enough to retire on a beach
and don't care anymore.
Yeah. Tell that to
Mrs. Baker.
Jordan: To be fair.
I'm pretty sure she
is on a beach right now.
You know what?
I have an idea.
Why don't we talk about
something else?
That's a great idea. babe.
probably one of your best.
Amina. I have barely seen you.
Tell me all about Dinsberg.
You know. this table is
a little crowded.
Come on. Khalil.
I'm guessing you haven't
told your pops about Dinsberg.
What gave it away?
His speech about how proud
of me he is?
He'll still be proud of you.
Maybe not right away.
but you need to tell him. Amina.
I know. I'm just waiting
for the right time.
And right now in front of
all of his friends is
certainly not that time.
I get that. but you
gotta do it soon.
He's gonna find out. Amina.
Khalil. why do you even care?
I thought we weren't friends
anymore. right?
[Adults laugh]
So what did London say
when you turned down
his job offer?
Mm. Not so loud.
Coop: Wait. Is this the job
offer Layla told me about?
Yes. London offered me
the head coach job at Beverly.
but Khalil does not know.
so please just
keep it down. all right?
Coop: I wish I didn't know.
I mean. this is gonna
ruin things with Cassius.
And you're abandoning
your wife on tour?
Coop. I can speak for myself.
Are you seriously
considering this?
I thought you didn't
want drama tonight.
Can we not talk about
the offer or Cassius?
[Doorbell rings]
Singer: ♪ All for you.
all for you ♪
♪ You. you. you.
and you. too... ♪
Layla: No. Jordan
didn't tell me
he invited you over
to work on the showcase.
Jordan: I didn't think
you would show up.
especially after I saw
who you were meeting with.
KJ: You guys. uh.
having a party?
Cassius: Yeah. it looks like
you're celebrating something.
Big decision maybe?
It's just dinner.
In fact. now that
you two are here.
you should stay.
Yeah. I could eat.
I'm not sure
there's enough room.
Let's hear it for
the cool kids' table. huh?
[Barks]
Give me something.
[Chuckles weakly]
No?
Uh. KJ. did your dad
tell you about
all the new recruiters coming
to the showcase?
Yeah. My dad tells me
everything you're up to.
OK.
Um. Amina. did you do
anything interesting today?
Please say yes.
Let's see. Today.
I stopped by your school.
where I had the sweetest.
sweetest conversation
with my dear friend Khalil.
I'm a terrible friend
and a terrible daughter.
I am the problem here.
After that. I went home
to study.
but then my dad forced me
to come here. so...
[Chuckles]
Wait. You went home
after South Crenshaw?
Yeah. Is that OK with you?
I'm sorry.
Is there something going on
I don't know about?
You know. Coach. I don't know.
Is there. Amina?
OK. you know what.
this is ridiculous.
Sorry. You... you can
have that.
Amina: Nope. It's fine.
Preach: Bet you don't
eat this good at school.
Breonna: I know I didn't.
Can we please not
talk about school?
Sorry. I... I thought
tonight was
supposed to be
a study break for me.
Great idea. Amina.
No more boring school talk.
Coop: Look. how about
we talk about
all this great food
Breonna brought?
Breonna: I can't take
all the credit.
Coop said she used to love
this as a kid.
Really? Coop said
she loved
umami-infused rib bites
as a kid?
Layla: You know. we don't need
to talk about food either.
Or talk at all.
Fine by me. all right?
How about we all
just finish our meals
without any more...
[Doorbell rings]
Come on!
Now what?
Tori: I hope I'm not
interrupting.
I just wanted to stop by
and give this packet to Khalil.
KJ? I didn't know
you were here.
Just full of
surprises. aren't you?
KJ: Um. yeah. yeah.
It all just kind of
happened last minute.
I see. It actually smells
really good in here.
Tori. you want to join us?
Sure.
Welcome to the kids' table.
So catch me up.
What'd I miss?
Khalil: Well.
KJ was gonna tell us
about his trip to the Bay.
Oh. great. KJ's barely told
me anything about it. So...
Hmm.
I mean. um...
nothing really happened.
I just hung out with my mom.
I... saw some friends.
It was... it was cool.
Yeah. KJ's mom lives
pretty close to Dinsberg.
right. Amina?
Surprised you two
didn't hook up.
I mean. it's like an hour away.
That's a lot of time.
Time reveals truth. right?
[Breonna and Coop chuckle]
Breonna: You know. I wish you
could've seen Coop
hold her own
with the other lawyers.
She was like a rock star.
Not surprising.
I mean. it ain't no
different than being onstage.
You just got to get
the crowd rooting for you.
and then. boom. mic drop.
More like gavel drop.
[Laughter]
Coop: Very nice.
Cassius: Hey. I got to say.
these might be the best
wings I've ever had.
Did you know that they
vent the boxes?
Clutch move.
Hey. listen. real quick.
I just want to say that
I know this dinner
didn't go exactly as planned.
And if that doorbell
rings one more time.
I'm probably gonna
lose it. but...
it really means a lot
to me that you guys are here
and I just...
Preach: Amina!
You must've lost your damn mind.
I give up.
I just got off the phone
with your dean at Dinsberg.
but apparently. I've already had
a long talk with him yesterday.
Is there something
you need to tell me?
Amina: Um...
Preach: Speak up.
[Softly]
There's no dead week.
Preach: I can't hear you.
I wrote an article
calling out Dinsberg
for staying silent
after an ICE raid.
They wouldn't let me publish it.
so I released it anonymously
online anyway.
Now I'm suspended
pending expulsion.
So you've been lying
to us this whole time?
Coop. I got this.
So you've been lying
to us this whole time?
Coop: Well said.
What the hell were you thinking?
I was thinking that Dinsberg.
a school that's already
on stolen land.
said nothing when ICE
took their custodian.
But I guess I'm the only one
who cares about that. right?
Well. I guess I'm the only one
who cares about your future.
'cause you threw it away
so damn casually.
Hold on. Preach. I know
you're upset. I am. too.
But she just stood up for
something she believed in.
Didn't you teach her that?
I didn't teach her to lie to me.
OK. I'm just saying.
there's nothing wrong
with doing what you
think is right.
I mean. Breonna. help me out.
Breonna: Honestly. I understand
where Preach is coming from.
That didn't help.
Breonna: Listen. opportunities
like Dinsberg.
they don't come around often
for Black girls like us. so...
I'm nothing like you.
I'm trying to make
a difference now.
not in 10 years.
when it'll be too late.
Well. the only thing you
gonna do is go home
and go to your room.
And just one last thing.
Which one of you fools
pretended to be me. huh?
Khalil knows better.
And my son wouldn't
do anything so...
KJ: It was me.
Cassius: dumb.
Oh. OK. Denzel.
How about you drop one
of your Preach gems?
No. how about this?
Pretend that I'm yelling
at a kid who's in trouble.
OK. let's take it easy
on poor KJ.
He's been telling so many lies.
he probably can't
keep them straight.
Um. Tori. let's go
get some air. OK?
Nope. I'm good.
[Chuckles]
You sure there's nothing
you want to tell me. KJ?
Or you. Amina?
KJ: Hey. um. can we maybe
go talk in private?
What kind of private?
Private like the conversation
you had in the hallway
with Amina earlier
or private like the dance you
had with Amina at Dinsberg?
Yeah. I found this on
the Dinsberg website:
#loveacrosstime.
Y'all see?
[Chuckles]
Yeah. there are a few.
but this one.
this one's my favourite.
KJ: Look. I'm sorry that
I didn't tell you.
but I only went because
it was an emergency.
What kind of emergency has
you rushing over to Dinsberg?
Well. she needed a date
for her dance.
[Chuckles]
Look. she organised
the whole thing.
and... and she spent
so much time
setting it up that.
look. she had no one to go with.
It's only an emergency
if it's your girlfriend.
Or if you. like...
Just tell me the truth.
Did something happen?
I can't believe I trusted you.
Tori. I'm sorry. OK?
It was a stupid mistake.
Khalil: Is there anybody
you not lying to?
I know you like to make
everything about you. Khalil.
but this isn't.
so stay out of it.
Did y'all sleep together?
KJ: What? No.
Amina: No.
Why should I believe
anything that you say?
We all know Amina's
a professional liar.
Just ask her dad.
Hey. can we just...
can we just go talk
someplace else?
Jordan: OK. guys. let's just
relax for a minute. OK?
I'm sure KJ did not mean...
I don't need you to talk for me.
In fact. I don't need
you talking to me.
Whoa. Jordan was
just trying...
Nah. nah. You keep talking
about Coach like that. bro.
we gonna have a issue.
Oh. your coach.
I guess he didn't tell
you about his job offer
to go coach at Beverly.
Say what?
Coach. is that true?
[Exhales]
Yeah.
How could you not tell me
you're leaving for Beverly?
Did you know about this?
Yes. I did. but I just...
Jordan: Look. I didn't want
to say anything
until it was for sure.
Cassius: Oh.
so it's for sure now?
Coop: Look. nothing is
definite yet.
We can do damage control
with Dinsberg.
Right. I am sure that
if Amina just apologises.
they would be open to...
Amina: Wait.
I'm not apologising
if I didn't do anything wrong.
Preach: You sure? 'Cause I
can think of a few things.
KJ: Look. I know
I messed up. It was dumb.
And yet what I still
haven't heard is
that it didn't mean anything.
Khalil: Just tell me the truth.
Are you going to Beverly?
Cassius:
Just be honest for once.
Layla: To be fair. I...
Jordan: Unlike you...
I have been nothing but upfront
since the beginning.
You are the one who's sneaking
around with Cliff Mosely
unless that was KJ
doing another impression.
Are you really working
with that scum?
Considering it.
So if you go to Beverly.
does that mean
I'm coming with you?
KJ: What. and take my spot?
Yeah. keep dreaming.
He's not taking your spot.
-So you are taking my job?
-So you're leaving me behind.
Jordan: I didn't say that!
Amina: You're not even
listening to me.
Won't you even read the article?
If you wanted me to read it.
I would've read it already.
Now you're gonna write
a letter to Dinsberg
saying how sorry you are.
That I will read.
Until then. I don't wanna
hear another word from you.
Hey. easy. Preach. Don't you
think that's a little harsh?
No. I think Preach
is just...
This is none of your business.
I'm sure you'd be
the first in line
to defend ICE if you could.
Layla: Enough. OK?
This has gotten way out of hand.
even for this house.
Everyone go to a corner
and cool off.
Now!
Hey. you leaving?
[Sighs]
Look. I don't need
to cool down. man.
And since KJ is
suddenly so interested
in private schools.
he needs to go home and study.
I'm sorry about tonight.
But maybe we can meet up
tomorrow.
I mean. we do still have
a showcase to plan.
I think I've heard enough
about your plans. man.
OK. I don't know how much
you really know about Cliff.
but he was gone from
the booster club for years
for a reason.
I wouldn't trust anything
that man says.
And I wouldn't trust London.
His loyalty is fickle.
So what now?
After everything.
we're just gonna go back
to hating each other?
I'll see you at the showcase.
Where are you going?
I'm not sure.
I haven't decided yet.
OK. I'm sorry
you found out this way.
OK. I didn't want
to say anything
because nothing is certain.
Khalil.
But you're considering it.
I am. Yeah.
It ju... it just. listen.
nothing will change
between us. I promise.
But you can't promise that.
If you're coaching at Beverly.
you'll be competing against me.
It'll be your job
to make sure I lose.
So explain to me.
how is that not
gonna change things?
[Door opens]
[Door shuts]
You definitely found
the best corner.
You know.
I was gonna go outside.
but that Tori girl
went that way.
She kinda scares me.
Well. look. I... I am sorry
about tonight.
I know it was a lot
different than our Ojai trip.
I know. right?
Thank God.
But I thought you
had a good time.
I did with you.
But you know what else is
great about Ojai. babe?
Pools and spas.
You know what we saw
none of? Pools or spas.
At least your friends
know how to have fun.
Fun? They argued
the entire time.
If I didn't love
hearing people argue.
I wouldn't be a lawyer.
Your friends are just
passionate. I like 'em.
Even Amina?
I still think she
could be a great lawyer.
But that was a family issue
that I was gonna stay out of
until someone asked me
what I thought
and then got upset when I
didn't agree with her.
You figured that out. huh?
You're a good lawyer.
More like I'm just good
at reading you.
Preach and I. we've always
had each other's backs.
And at the time we didn't.
I just hoped it'd be you
that did.
I'm sorry it felt like that.
but you're never going
to have somebody's back
by just agreeing with
everything they say.
So I get to disagree
with you now.
Of course. of course.
Listen. no one understands
what Preach has been through
more than you.
He's had to fight for
everything his whole life.
And I think he just wants
better for Amina.
There is nothing wrong
with that.
Oh. You are
a good lawyer.
[Both chuckle]
Thank you.
[Chuckles]
I hope you know how sorry I am.
I'm not sure I know you
at all anymore.
Please. Would you
just read the article?
I know you'll understand.
Is there anything
in that article that says
it's OK to lie to me.
to my face repeatedly?
I thought we had
a good relationship.
I thought we trusted each other.
I was gonna tell you tonight.
but then dinner happened.
What about the other times
in the 3 days you been home?
Look. I wanted
to tell you the truth
so many times.
I was just afraid
how you'd react.
[Exhales]
After everything
we been through...
it just sucks that you
didn't think I'd understand.
And that broke my heart.
I'm guessing you don't want
to hear my Preach impression
right now.
Good guess.
Look. I shouldn't
have argued with you
in front of Amina.
That's my fault.
That was a family issue.
Nah. You family. Coop.
I appreciate you.
But you know the good thing
about family is
they forgive you
even when you messed up.
No. She messed up bad.
Coop.
Come on. She ain't
mess up that bad.
Look at me.
Ain't nobody get shot.
Look. I can't say that I ain't
never lied to my parents.
but when I did. it was usually
because I was scared.
That's what Amina is
right now... scared.
And she did something she
thought you would be proud of.
and she got suspended for it.
Am I supposed to be
proud of her for this?
Not at all.
You are supposed to make sure
that she knows
you got her back no matter what
and that she's not
in this alone.
And maybe read the damn article.
Gonna be all right. man.
[Exhales]
[Dog barks]
[Sighs]
What'd you think?
It was really good.
I just wish I was
the first one to read it
instead of the last.
Yeah.
I do. too.
So you saw ICE take them
and nobody tried to stop it?
Nobody did a thing.
[Exhales]
Man. you gonna find out
this world is full of people
that are vindictive.
stupid. scared.
and all of the above.
But you've got to be
better than them.
Dad. I just couldn't
stay silent.
Well. you don't have
to be silent.
Just be smart.
You think I'm cool
with every decision
my bosses at South Crenshaw
High School make?
But I don't quit.
I don't get myself fired
because I know I can do
more good for those kids
if I stay.
And everyone at Dinsberg
is always talking about
how we're one big family.
Once I realised that was a lie.
I just...
I got so angry.
I get it.
But every fight is
not your fight.
Right now I just need
for you to be 16
and not take on the world's
problems all by yourself.
and I promise we'll get
through this together.
No snooty school's gonna
mess up my girl's future.
[Chuckles]
Thank you. Dad.
But for now. you are grounded.
You do not leave this house
without me by your side.
You hear me?
Yes.
Consider me like
an ankle bracelet.
You get too far away. I go off.
You hear me?
Yes. sir.
Love you. old man.
I love you. too.
[Chuckles]
Singer:
♪ Is this what you wanted? ♪
♪ You can fake it.
I can fake it hardly... ♪
He said he hasn't decided yet.
But will by this weekend.
I mean. if he ain't
turn it down by now.
he's probably not going to.
Hey. but don't sweat it. man.
A superstar like you gonna have
a bunch of coaches in your life.
But you only got one family.
Jordan was the whole
reason I made QB.
If he leaves. what's
gonna happen to my spot?
He ain't the one
with the power. man.
He ain't in charge.
Coach Bobby knows who the best
player on the team is.
Ain't that right?
That's right.
I'm really glad you called.
I'm not promising anything.
You don't have to.
I'm just glad you knew
we'd be here for you
when you needed us.
I'mma get us something to drink.
What'd I tell you?
I knew Baker was gonna screw up.
Our son is hurting right now.
It's nothing to celebrate.
Um. thanks for staying
to help clean.
No problem.
It's the least I could do.
I mean. dinner was my idea.
And it's not like I'm in a rush
to get home to Preach and Amina.
I saw you and Breonna made up.
You really should get
a wall in this kitchen.
She said she had a fun time.
which is not the word
I would use
to describe tonight.
The night didn't go as planned.
but it was still a success.
No. I wouldn't use
that word either.
Look. Breonna had fun
with your friends.
and everybody likes her
and is really excited
for you two.
including me.
I'm sorry that I
questioned your happiness.
It's all good.
I mean. you were just
looking out. right?
Plus. I hear that's
what good friends do.
Yes. And good friends
support each other
no matter what.
I'm really glad you're happy.
Thank you.
Hiding in the bushes?
You've gone from liar
to stalker really quickly.
I was just waiting
for you to get home.
Not helping your stalker case.
I just wanted to
talk to you in private.
I don't have
anything else to say to you.
As far as I'm concerned.
you and Amina are both liars.
who deserve each other.
There is nothing going on
between me and Amina.
It was one mistake.
Singer: ♪ True I'm unstable ♪
♪ Picking up the pieces... ♪
Tori. please. you know me.
Or you know I'm not
that type of guy
that lies and cheats.
OK. it was really a mistake.
We got caught up
in a stupid moment
and... and it didn't even
mean anything.
Look. it'll never happen again.
Singer: ♪ Hope you think
of me often... ♪
You know what's sad?
Is I can't tell if you're
lying to me or to yourself.
Whatever.
I don't care anymore.
Bye. KJ.
Wait. Tori...
Singer:
♪ Tryin' to stay whole ♪
♪ I'm just tryin'
to stay whole ♪
Oh. for sure.
Piece of cake. Yeah.
He's here now.
Yeah. I'll get back to you.
Oh. wow.
I got to tell you.
I am so glad you called me.
It seems not everyone is onboard
with London's decision.
And do you know what that means?
We can finally get rid
of Jordan Baker.
Where do we start?
Greg. move your head.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today